## Software Engineer\ CONCOVIVONO

TEMPORARY ADDRESS Jl. Sadang Luhur No. 48 • Sekeloa • Coblong • Bandung
MAIL condro@outlook.co.id

PHONE +62 85773746786

PROFILE AND SKILLS

Able to talk with C/C++, PHP, Golang, Ruby, Javascript(Node and Vue)

Able to design, implement, and query mySQL & mongoDB Familiar using Git, Terminal, Team Collaboration Tools including Atlassian, Jira & Basecamp

Experienced in building REST API, Vue Front End, and being Fullstack Web Developer

Skilled using various libraries including PHP Laravel, Ruby on Rails, or building from from scratch

**EDUCATION** 

Institut Teknologi Bandung 2015-present

Bachelor's Degree - Sistem dan Teknologi Informasi

SMA N SBBS (Sragen Bilingual Boarding School) 2012-2015

High School - Science

Delta Koleji - Samsun, Turkey 2012-2013

Students Exchange Programs

and Cultural Center Bandung

AWARDS / HONORS

Best Idea 2018
University Internal Event (Inkubator IT Idea Challenge)
Top Five C-GEN Festival for Smart City 2018

Smart City Competition held in UNIDUS

**EXPERIENCES** 

Back End Engineer [Intern] • Bukalapak.com

Back End Engineer [Part Time] • meridian.id

Teaching Assistant • Basic Software Engineering
Course and Software Development Course - ITB
Laboratory Assistant • Software Engineering

Summer 2018
early 2018 and
early 2019
2016-present

Treasurer • Learning and Cultural Center Bandung

Web Developer and Web Master • Learning

2015-2019

2015-2019

**PROJECTS** 

Tweak (fitness app center)

with Meridian.id • build API, Android, and Front-End (2 side app)

May 2018

Microservice: Seller Acquisition

for Bukalapak.com • built using GoLang and Ruby on Rails

Aug 2018

Knowledge Base Contact Center Badan POM RI
with Meridian.id • built for BPOM RI using Laravel

MBWG Webpage • Redesign official website of

2017

**MBWG Webpage** • Redesign official website of Marching Band ITB, built using Wordpress

**Festival Paduan Suara PSM-ITB 2017 •** Sep 2016 - Competition Web Registration Portal, built using Laravel Feb 2017

BPJS Questionnaire Website • Digitalize the questionnaire of BPJS Kesehatan Indonesia, built using Laravel

MTI ITB Official Webpage • Blog and Member Portal for Sep 2016 -

MTI ITB Official Webpage • Blog and Member Portal for Sep 2016 Industrial Engineering Students ITB, built using Wordpress and Laravel Jan 2017

**Liga Medika UI 2017** • Competition Registration Web Portal 2016 for Medical Science University of Indonesia, built using Laravel